http://www.ibspayroll.com/terms.php

IBS Payroll Terms and Conditions
"Your preferred local Payroll and Tax Service Provider since 1991"
Call us:
(707) 586-4300
HomeProducts & ServicesServices at a GlanceHuman Resources ManagementBenefits ManagementPayroll & Tax Services Time & Labor ManagementMobile ApplicationsMarketplace Add-onsThird Party AccessAbout UsInnovative Business SolutionsMeet The TeamThe HistoryOur Mission and VisionPhilantropic WorkDirectionsContactBlogVisit our blogResourcesFAQFormsAbout FormsIBS FormsFederal FormsCalifornia FormsNewslettersExternal ResourcesSystem StatusLoginLogin
REGISTER COMPANY
Company Name
Company Id
First Email Id
Second Email ID
Third Email ID
Fourth Email ID
Agree to use email communication service
Email ID
WebHCMSharefileContactRequest InformationRequest SupportContact Information
HomeProducts & ServicesServices at a GlanceHuman Resources ManagementBenefits ManagementPayroll & Tax Services Time & Labor ManagementMobile ApplicationsMarketplace Add-onsThird Party AccessAbout UsInnovative Business SolutionsMeet The TeamThe HistoryOur Mission and VisionPhilantropic WorkDirectionsContactBlogVisit our blogResourcesFAQFormsAbout FormsIBS FormsFederal FormsCalifornia FormsNewslettersExternal ResourcesSystem StatusLoginLogin
REGISTER COMPANY
Company Name
Company Id
First Email Id
Second Email ID
Third Email ID
Fourth Email ID
Agree to use email communication service
Email ID
WebHCMSharefileContactRequest InformationRequest SupportContact Information
Request a quote today!
(707) 586-4300
Terms
- Disclaimer: All material included in the Innovative Business Solutions, Inc. website ("Website”) is for informational purposes only, and may not reflect the most current practices in the areas of Payroll, Time and Attendance, or Human Resource administration. The information contained herein is not offered as legal or any other advice on any particular matter. IBS and the contributing authors expressly disclaim any liability to any person with respect to any consequences of anything done or omitted to be done in reliance upon the contents of the Website. No client or other reader should act or refrain from acting on the basis of any matter contained in the Website without seeking the appropriate legal or other professional advice on the particular facts and circumstances at issue. IBS is not responsible for any third party content which can be accessed through the Website.
- Links: Hypertext links are provided as a service to users and are not sponsored by or affiliated with this site. The links are to be accessed at the user’s own risk, and the authors of the Website make no representations or warranties about the content of these links.
- Privacy: Use of the Website is governed by its Terms of Use. As set forth in the Terms of Use, this document discloses the privacy practices (the "Privacy Policy”) of Innovative Business Solutions, Inc., the provider of the Website. Please read the information below to learn what information IBS collects and how it is used.
IBS collects two types of information about our visitors to the Website: Personally Identifiable information, and Non-Personally Identifiable information.
1) Personally Identifiable Information refers to the information that allows IBS to know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities such as requesting a quote for services, you may provide certain information about yourself.
2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. IBS may gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on the Website. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. Examples of the kind of information that may be collected include the uniform resource locator ("URL”) for the internal site that you just came from, which URL you go to next, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP”) address. The Website also may store cookies on your computer.
IBS does not collect any Personally Identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily provide it. In addition, IBS may also collect, either directly or indirectly, certain Non-Personally Identifiable information. In general, IBS uses this information to learn where visitors to the Website come from, how they interact with the Website and to generate reports about the use and interaction with the Website.
IBS does not sell, trade or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to others. Subject to the law, regulations and rules of professional conduct governing business practices in the State of California, IBS may provide Personally Identifiable information to third parties who provide services for the mutual benefit of IBS and its clients.
Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information by IBS. Other sites accessible through this Website have their own Privacy Policies and their own data collection, use, and disclosure practices. IBS is not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.
From time to time, IBS may need to change this Privacy Policy. You can determine if this Privacy Policy has been revised since your last visit by referring to the "Revision Date” at the top of this Website page. Your continued use of the Website after such modifications constitutes your agreement to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact IBS by sending a letter to:
Innovative Business Solutions, Inc.
Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer
6400 Redwood Drive, Suite 100
Rohnert Park, CA 94928
Request More Information
Services at a Glance
Human Resources Management
Payroll & Tax Services
Time & Labor Management
Mobile Applications
Marketplace Add-ons
Call our team of experts today (707) 586-4300
Gina Bedrosian, Personnel Administrator, Tierracast
"WebTime has made the payroll process incredibly easy! It is user friendly and both supervisors and employees alike enjoy the ability to see their data in "real time". IBS Payroll made the changeover process a smooth transition...
Read more >>
Our most popular toolsOnline payrollPerformance evaluationsApplicant trackingOnline timesheetsPayroll tax filingMobile AppWhy businesses choose us
"Since its inception, Innovative Business Solutions, Inc. has had essentially zero turnover, either in its staff or customer base. This circumstance has created a remarkable record of consistency and continuity in dealing with clients.
Innovative Bus..."
Find out more...What we doHuman Resources ManagementPayroll & Tax ServicesTime & Labor ManagementThird Party AccessContact Us
© 2020 IBS - Innovative Business Solutions - All Right Reserved - Mission Statement and Vision -
Terms and Conditions
Designed by Business Website Center
